hrberry.com 2019-05-04

# Privacy Policy

##### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to Ascent Consulting Services Private Limited, hereinafter referred to as AscentHR. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that AscentHR collects, and the ways in which AscentHR uses that personal information.

##### Personal information collection

AscentHR may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  1. Personally Identifiable Information (PII) like Employee ID, Name, Address, Age, Date of birth, Social Security Number etc., and Financial Information like Employee Salary related data
  2. This is an Employee Self Service Portal for Human Resource Management & Payroll related information for service delivery by AscentHR, which include self-declaration & self-service management by Employees / Managers and other agreed stakeholders of our Clients.
  3. End user subscription, Employee registration & deregistration processes are controlled by AscentHR internal processes as per validly executed subsisting Master Service Agreement (MSA) or Contract with our client.
  4. First time registration is mandatory for all employees.
  5. Password policy applies to all employees.
  6. Employee can reset their credentials any time and they may also be forced to change password as per AscentHR Password Policy.
  7. Web portal is used by employee to check their profile, pay details, tax information, process leave & reimbursement application etc.,
  8. The information that you provide during first time registration shall be your E-mail ID, Secret Question, Date of birth and password. These information are maintained within our application.
  9. As part of self service module being delivered to Employees, you may view or update some transaction data which are PII or Salary related financial information as said above in (1)
  10. We abide by the confidentiality & data privacy assurances provided in our Master Service Agreement (MSA) or Contracts

##### Using personal information

AscentHR may use your personal information to:

  * Deliver HR Information Systems which encompasses employee life cycle management
  * Collect information related to Payroll & Benefits Processing
  * Provide such regulatory of other required information under the Master Services Agreement or Contract
  * Provide mobile enabled employee self-services

AscentHR shall NOT discloses your personal & financial information to any agents or sub-contractors for any purposes other than for which is legally required as per the contract or the prevailing laws of India

TAscentHR shall be using Cookies in its website to store user preferences and settings, so that you don’t get asked for the same information you’ve already given to the site.

##### Securing your data

AscentHR will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

AscentHR will store all the personal information you provide on our servers hosted within AscentHR Data centre which is Fully Owned and Managed by AscentHR Internal Employees. We DO NOT engage any third party vendors, or sub-contractors in service delivery or critical administration activity.

Information that are transmitted via our network, stored on our devices are encrypted

##### Cross-border data transfers

Information that AscentHR collects are stored and processed within India. In addition, information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world. AscentHR use of the information in accordance with this IT Act 2008 India.

You agree to such cross-border access to information.

##### Updating this statement

AscentHR may update this privacy statement by posting a new version on this website.:

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

##### Other websites

This website may have link to other web sites that are fully owned and managed by AscentHR. This web site will NOT have links to any third party websites.

##### Data Protection Authority

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA) and believe we maintain your personal data subject to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you may direct questions or complaints to our data protection office (DPO) at below mentioned contact details

##### Contact AscentHR

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please write:

  * by email to info@ascent-online.com;
  * by URL http://www.ascent-online.com
